Guide to the Duke University Union Records, 1954-ongoing UA.09.13.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University Union records
1954-ongoing
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Union
UA.09.13.0001
115.5 Linear Feet
Collection contains records of the Duke University Union (1954-ongoing), a student-run organization at Duke University, concerning all manner of operations and events sponsored by the Union. Within the collection are records related to student life at Duke, symposia put on by the Union, and social and academic events sponsored by the Union. The collection also contains numerous scrapbooks documenting Union events, members, and history from the 1950s through the mid-2000s.
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. There may be a 24-hour delay in obtaining these materials.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the University Archives to use this collection.
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Duke University Union Records were received by the University Archives as a series of transfers.
Historical Note
The Duke University Union was founded in 1954 as part of the Office of Student Affairs. Eventually, it morphed into a wholly student-run organization, which it remains today.
Collection Overview
The earliest records in the collection date to the early 1950s, before the Duke University Union was officially founded. The bulk of the records date from the 1960s through the 1990s, and deal with general Union operations, as well as Union-sponsored events.
Among the events represented in the collection are numerous concerts and symposia. During the 1960s and 1970s, the Union sponsored an annual symposium that dealt with contemporary issues and problems. These events frequently drew notable speakers, ranging from Allen Dulles to Ralph Ellison. Concerts were also regularly scheduled and sponsored by the Union. Some of the bands represented in the collection include the Grateful Dead, the Dave Matthews Band, Gordon Lightfoot, and R.E.M. Among the recurring events that the Union sponsored and are represented in the collection are Joe College, Oktoberfest, an annual tree lighting in December, and Springfest (now the Last Day of Classes celebration).
Finally, performing and visual arts are both well-represented in the collection. The Union sponsored frequent performances of plays and musicals, as well as shows by local, national, and international artists. The Broadway at Duke series was also sponsored by the Union and is represented in the collection.
Materials are organized in a loose chronological fashion. There are instances wherein it made more intellectual sense to deviate from strict chronological order at both the folder and box level, and this is represented in the arrangement.
Related Material
Major Speakers Committee Records
Duke University Archives
Major Attractions Committee Records
Duke University Archives
Quadrangle Pictures Records
Duke University Archives
Ella Fountain Pratt Papers
Duke University Archives
Trinity College (Durham, N.C.) -- Alumni and alumnae; Duke University -- Alumni and alumnae; Duke University -- History -- 20th century; Duke University. Union; Duke University. Union
- General Records1954-ongoing, 54 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  Series contains the general records of the Duke University Union, from before its inception through the 2000s. Records are mostly paper and contain information about the operation of the Union and its committees.
  - Union History - Research (active), 1954-1972 (Box 1)
  - Trust Fund Financial Records, circa 1937-1968 (Box 1)
  - Association of College Unions - Manuals, 1948 (Box 1)
  - University Union letterhead, undated (Box 1)
  - Building Committee Planning Records, 1946-1953 (Box 1)
  - Building, 1946-1964 (Box 1)
  - Association of College Unions - Region IV Conferences, 1951-1954 (Box 1)
  - B.O.G. Unfilled Membership Applications, undated (Box 1)
  - The Regions Analyze the Union's Job (sect II of outline), 1952 (Box 1)
  - DUU Director's Report, 1954-1955 (Box 1)
  - Board of Governor's Minutes, 1954-1955 (Box 1)
  - Board of Governor's Correspondence: general, undated (Box 1)
  - Board of Governor's Correspondence, 1954 (Box 1)
  - Dance Bands - General Artists Corp. Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous - Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 1)
  - Dance Bands - Associated Booking Corporation, 1954-1955 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Prospective Speakers on Agency, 1954-1955 (Box 1)
  - Recreation Committee Meeting Minutes, 1955-1961 (Box 1)
  - Recreation Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 1)
  - College Day 1955 Duke Promotional Materials/Admissions Materials, 1955 (Box 1)
  - Artists - Alkahest Celebrity Bureau, 1955-1956 (Box 1)
  - DUU Director's Report, 1955-1956 (Box 1)
  - Board of Governors Minutes, 1955-1956 (Box 1)
  - Art Room (209 Flowers), 1955 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1955-1956 (Box 1)
  - Student Lecture Coordinating Board, 1955-1956 (Box 1)
  - Association of College Unions - Region IV Conference, 1955-1957 (Box 1)
  - Association of College Unions - Annual Conferences, 1955-1964 (Box 1)
  - Association of College Unions - Region IV Newsletters, 1956-1963 (Box 1)
  - Academic Averages of Various Campus Activities and Organizations, 1955-1963 (Box 1)
  - Artists - Misc. Correspondence, 1956-1963 (Box 1)
  - Role of the College Union, 1956 (Box 1)
  - Admissions Office - H.S. Visitations, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - B.O.G. Old Applications, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - Board of Governors Minutes, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - Board of Governors Correspondence, 1956 (Box 1)
  - Certificates of Merit, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - Charles C. Peterson (Billiards Tours), 1955-1957 (Box 1)
  - Dance Bands - General Artists Corp. Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - Dance Bands - Associated Booking Corporation Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - Bookstore Records, circa 1956 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Chief Justice Earl Warren, 1956 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: General, 1956 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Mr. Paul Butler, 1956 (Box 1)
  - Duke Diplomats Bermuda Trip, 1956 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: List of Speakers, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Thank-you Letters, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Dr. Ralph Bunche, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Dr. Karl Gruber, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Bruce Cotton, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Composities, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Harold Stassen, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: John Foster Dulles, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Biographical Data - Pictures, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - Misc. - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - Eighth Annual Conference at Duke, 1957 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Seminar, 1957 (Box 1)
  - DUU Director's Report, 1957-1958 (Box 1)
  - B.O.G. Old Applications: Letters of Acceptance or Rejection, 1957-1958 (Box 1)
  - Board of Governors Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 1)
  - Board of Governors Minutes, 1957-1958 (Box 1)
  - Board of Governors Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 1)
  - Personnel Rolls, 1957-1958 (Box 1)
  - Publicity Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 1)
  - Region IV Rep, 1957-1958 (Box 1)
  - Region IV Conference, 1957 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1957-1958 (Box 1)
  - Artists - Alkahest Celebrity Bureau, 1957-1958 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Harry S Truman, 1957 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Molly Flynn, 1957 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Dr. Gerald Clemence, 1957 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Ogden Nash, 1957 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Rep. Kenneth B. Keating, 1957 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Pres. Dwight D. Eisenhower, 1957 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Justice William O. Douglas, 1957 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Thomas E. Dewey, 1957 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: E.B. White, 1957 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Adlai Stevenson, 1957-1958 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: James T. Farrell, 1957-1958 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Prospective Speakers, 1957-1958 (Box 1)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Publicity Letters to Other Schools, 1957-1958 (Box 2)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Sir Leslie Munro, 1957-1958 (Box 2)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Fayez Sayegh, 1957-1958 (Box 2)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: George W. Britt (contact), 1957-1958 (Box 2)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Walt Kelly, 1957-1958 (Box 2)
  - Ride Bureau, 1957-1958 (Box 2)
  - Giesen & Boomer (Artist Management Co.), 1957-1958 (Box 2)
  - Misc. - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 2)
  - Board of Governors Administrative Records, 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - Board of Governors Minutes and Agendas, 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - B.O.G. Summary Minutes, 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - B.O.G. Reports, 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - Student Conference on US Affairs (at West Point), 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - Misc. Western Union, 1955-1959 (Box 2)
  - B.O.G. Workshop Information, 1959 (Box 2)
  - Personnel Rolls, 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - Dance Bands - General Artists Corp. Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - Region IV Correspondence, 1959 (Box 2)
  - Symposium Committee: Minutes, 1958-1960 (Box 2)
  - Symposium Proposal, 1958 (Box 2)
  - Spring Banquet, April 21, 1959 (Box 2)
  - Region IV Newsletter Material, 1959 (Box 2)
  - Association of College Unions - Region IV Conferences, 1958-1960 (Box 2)
  - Conference (Regional), 1959 (Box 2)
  - Misc. - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 2)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Walter P. Reuther, 1957-1959 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - Recreation Committee, 1958-1960 (Box 2)
  - Dance Bands: Associated Booking Corporation Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - Symposium Committee: "U.S. - Soviet Conflict" Miscellaneous, 1959 (Box 2)
  - Symposium Committee: "U.S. - Soviet Conflict" Report on Mechanical Details, 1959 (Box 2)
  - Symposium Committee: "U.S. - Soviet Conflict" Miscellaneous, 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Bertrand Russell, 1958 (Box 2)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Harrison Salisburg, 1958 (Box 2)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Prof. Arthur Larson, 1958 (Box 2)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: General, 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Attorney General Rogers, 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Board of Governors Reports, 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Speakers and Rosters, 1956-1958 (Box 2)
  - Symposium Committee: "U.S. - Soviet Conflict," Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 2)
  - Symposium Committee: "U.S. - Soviet Conflict," Speakers, Dr. Merle Fainsod, 1959 (Box 2)
  - Banquet, December 9, 1959 (Box 2)
  - Duke Univ. Symposium Comm: "The U.S. - Soviet Conflict", October 1959 (Box 2)
  - Symposium Committee: "U.S. - Soviet Conflict," Substantive Evaluation, 1959 (Box 2)
  - Symposium Committee: "U.S. - Soviet Conflict," Prospective Speakers, 1959 (Box 2)
  - Symposium Committee: "U.S. - Soviet Conflict," Members, 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - Symposium Committee: "U.S. - Soviet Conflict," Speakers, Mr. Thomas Whitney, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - Symposium Committee: "U.S. - Soviet Conflict," Speakers, Dr. Frederick Schuman, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - Soviet Student Visit, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - Charlotte Poster Exchange Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 2)
  - Quadrangle Pictures: Carolina Delivery Service, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - Board of Governors Administrative Records, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - B.O.G. Old Applications: Letters of Acceptance or Rejection, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - B.O.G. Letters of Acceptance and Rejection, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - B.O.G. Summary Minutes, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - Board of Governors Minutes and Agendas, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - Board of Governors Student Leadership Conference, 1959-1961 (Box 2)
  - Building Commission, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - Current Info - Hansen, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - Duke Film Society, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - Recreation Committee: Bridge Club, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - Publicity Ideas, 1959 (Box 2)
  - Association of College Unions - Correspondence, 1960-1964 (Box 2)
  - Region IV Conference, 1960 (Box 2)
  - Christmas Buffet, December 9, 1959 (Box 2)
  - Spring Banquet, April 19, 1960 (Box 2)
  - Artists - Alkahest Celebrity Bureau, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: James Hagerty, 1957-1960 (Box 2)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: George V. Allen, 1957-1960 (Box 2)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Walter Cronkite, 1957-1960 (Box 2)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Quincy Mumford (Library of Congress), 1957-1960 (Box 2)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: General, 1959 (Box 2)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Robert Elegant -- Red China, 1959 (Box 2)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Dr. Ralph E. Lapp, 1959 (Box 2)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Malcolm L. Denise, 1959 (Box 2)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: The Honorable Hugh Gaitskell, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: General, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: George V. Allen, "The New Diplomacy", 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Sir Herbert Read, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Senator John Kennedy, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - DUU Director's Report, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - Personnel Rolls, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - Dance Bands: Music Corporation of America, 1954-1961 (Box 2)
  - Cotton Bowl Classic, 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Artists - Misc. Advertising Materials, 1960-1963 (Box 2)
  - College Quiz Bowl, 1960 (Box 2)
  - Quadrangle Pictures: Carolina Delivery Service, 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - DUU Director's Report, 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - B.O.G. - Old Applications: Letters of Acceptance or Rejection, 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Board of Governors Minutes and Agendas, 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Board of Governors Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Building Commission, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Committee Reports, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Dance Bands: General Arts Corp. Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Lectures and Programs Records, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Personnel Rolls, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Workshop, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Banquet, December 7, 1960 (Box 3)
  - Spring Banquet, April 24, 1961 (Box 3)
  - Constitution, 1961 (Box 3)
  - Union Yearly Report, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - French Exhibit, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Symposium Committee: Minutes, 1960 (Box 3)
  - Symposium: Herberg Transcript, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Symposium Committee: "Post-Christian Man", 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Symposium Committee: "Post-Christian Man" Miscellaneous, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Symposium Committee: "Post-Christian Man" Miscellaneous (folder 2), 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Symposium Committee: "Post-Christian Man" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Symposium Committee: "Post-Christian Man" Members Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Symposium Committee: "Post-Christian Man" Speakers, Dr. Walter A. Kaufman, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Symposium Committee: "Post-Christian Man" Speakers, Dr. Stanley R. Hopper, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Symposium Committee: "Post-Christian Man" Speakers, Prof. Will Herberg, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Symposium Committee: "Post-Christian Man" Speakers, Prospective Speakers, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Senator Douglas, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Senator John F. Kennedy (2nd Visit), 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Dr. Benjamin R. Mays, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Virginia Peterson, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: William Faulkner, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Adlai Stevenson, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: General, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Ambassador Romulo, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Ambassador Boland, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: General Thomas D. White, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Correspondence/Steve Braswell, Chairman, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Nehru, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Fraternity Mail Summer, 1961 (Box 3)
  - Constitutions, 1961, 1965, 1970 (Box 3)
  - Box Office Records, 1961-1967 (Box 3)
  - Union & Chairman Material: Chuck Routh, House Committee Chairman, 1959-1961 (Box 3)
  - House Committee: Special Services Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - House Committee: Special Services Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Records (Pratt Files), 1961-1962 (Box 3)
  - Artists - Alkahest Celebrity Bureau, 1961-1962 (Box 3)
  - Board of Governors Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 3)
  - Board of Governors Minutes and Agendas, 1961-1962 (Box 3)
  - Recreation Committee, 1961 (Box 3)
  - Special Services Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 3)
  - Recreation Committee: Joe College Picnic, April 27, 1962 (Box 3)
  - Building Commission, 1961-1962 (Box 3)
  - DUU Director's Report, 1961-1962 (Box 3)
  - Personnel Rolls, 1961-1962 (Box 3)
  - Christmas Buffet, December 13, 1961 (Box 3)
  - Symposium Committee: "The Commonwealth of Children", 1961-1962 (Box 3)
  - Symposium Committee: 1961 Symposium, "The Commonwealth of Children", 1961-1962 (Box 3)
  - Quadrangle Pictures: Carolina Delivery Service, 1961-1962 (Box 3)
  - NCAA Golf Tournament Reservations, 1961-1962 (Box 3)
  - NCAA Golf Tournament, 1961-1962 (Box 3)
  - Symposium Committee: Minutes, 1961-1962 (Box 3)
  - Symposium Committee: Miscellaneous, including minutes, 1961-1962 (Box 3)
  - Symposium Committee: "Power Structures: Context for Creativity?" Membership Applications RESTRICTED, 1961-1962 (Box 3)
  - Symposium Committee: "Power Structures: Context for Creativity?" Speakers, Dr. Edward J. Shoben, Jr., 1961-1962 (Box 3)
  - Symposium Committee: "Power Structures: Context for Creativity?" Proceedings, 1961-1962 (Box 3)
  - Peace Corps Records, Miscellaneous, 1961-1962 (Box 3)
  - Association of College & University Concert Managers - Executive Cmte, 1961-1963 (Box 3)
  - Duke Union Philosophy Statement, undated (Box 3)
  - Special Events Committee: Last Lecture Series, Tom Cordle, March 13, 1962 (Box 3)
  - Special Events Committee: Last Lecture Series, General Records, 1962-1967 (Box 3)
  - Symposium Committee: "Power Structures: Context for Creativity?" and "Dimensions of Defense", 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Symposium Committee: "Power Structures: Context for Creativity?" Speakers, Mr. Moorhead Wright, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Symposium Committee: "Power Structures: Context for Creativity?" Miscellaneous, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Symposium Committee: "Power Structures: Context for Creativity?" Miscellaneous Duke Faculty Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Symposium Committee: "Power Structures: Context for Creativity?" Faculty Member Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Symposium Committee: "Power Structures: Context for Creativity?" Proposed Speakers, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Symposium Committee: "Power Structures: Context for Creativity?" Speakers, Mr. John Ciardi, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Lt. General Dean Strother, USAF Chief of Operations, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Henry Kissinger, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: "World in Focus" Sorenson-Hammond, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Inst. Of Contemporary Arts (Colin Wilson), 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Paul W. Gross, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Allen Drury, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Yale Russian Chorus, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Allen W. Dulles, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Sir Abu Bakar (Nigerian Prime Minister), 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Charles Malik, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: William J. Lederer, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Willy Brandt, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: General, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Ambassador Bourguiba, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Edward R. Murrow, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Norman Thomas, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Karl Shapiro, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Dr. Schwarz-Liebermann, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Sir Patrick Dean, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Communist Speaker, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Graphic Arts: Photographic Exhibits, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Symposium Committee: "Dimensions of Defense," Papers on Defense, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Symposium Committee: "Dimensions of Defense," Speakeres, Dr. Thomas C. Schelling, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Symposium Committee: "Dimensions of Defense," Applications for Committee, RESTRICTED, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Symposium Committee: "Dimensions of Defense," Miscellaneous, 1960-1962 (Box 4)
  - Symposium Committee: "Dimensions of Defense," Speakers, Prof. Kenneth E. Boulding, 1962 (Box 4)
  - Symposium Committee: "Dimensions of Defense," Speakers, Allen W. Dulles, 1962 (Box 4)
  - Symposium Committee: "Dimensions of Defense," Proposed Speakers, 1962 (Box 4)
  - Symposium Committee: "Dimensions of Defense," Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Symposium Committee: "Regional Implications of Space", May 1962 (Box 4)
  - African Seminar, 1962 (Box 4)
  - Spring Banquet, April 25, 1962 (Box 4)
  - Board of Governors Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Babysitting Service, 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Special Services Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Board of Governors Minutes and Agendas, 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Board of Governors Administrative and Meeting Records, 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Building Commission, 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Lectures and Programs Records, 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Secretarial Workshop, February 9, 1963 (Box 4)
  - Dance Bands: General Arts Corp. Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Peace Corps Records, Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Brochures/Miscellaneous Records, 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Art Exhibits, 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Dr. Jorge Castellanos, 1962 (Box 4)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Margaret Mead, 1962 (Box 4)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Franz Josef Strauss, 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: General, 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Last Lecture Series, 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Symposium Committee: Minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Dance Bands: Associated Booking Corporation Correspondence, 1960-1963 (Box 4)
  - Quadrangle Pictures: Carolina Delivery Service, 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Newsletters, 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Special Services Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 4)
  - Duke Tour 1962 [European Summer Trip], 1962 (Box 4)
  - Experiment in International Living, 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Board of Governors Administrative Files, 1963-1964 (Box 4)
  - Boards of Chairmen and Governors Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1963-1964 (Box 4)
  - Board of Governors Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 4)
  - B.O.G.--Applications, Letters of Acceptance or Rejection, undated (Box 4)
  - National Intercollegiate Table Tennis Tournament Plaque, 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Performing Arts Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 5)
  - Performing Arts Committee, circa 1962 (Box 5)
  - Fine Arts Committee: Art Exhibit Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 5)